http://www.sqlexcel.net/privacy-policy/

Skip to content Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use 1. Terms By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law. 2. Use License Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:modify or copy the materials;use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s web site;remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; ortransfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format. 3. Disclaimer The materials on SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s web site are provided “as is”. SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site. 4. Limitations In no event shall SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s Internet site, even if SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net or a SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you. 5. Revisions and Errata The materials appearing on SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials. 6. Links SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk. 7. Site Terms of Use Modifications SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use. 8. Governing Law Any claim relating to SQL Excel – sqlexcel.net’s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Oregon without regard to its conflict of law provisions. General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site. Privacy Policy Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.Sponsor AdSponsor AdSponsor AdSponsor Ad Kennedy Tax Solutions - IRS Tax Attorney OregonPortland OregonSalem OregonBend OregonEugene Oregon WashingtonSeattle WABellevue WATacoma WAVancouver WAOlympia WASpokane WACalifornia:San FranciscoOaklandFreemontSan Jose ReddingSacramentoElk GroveStocktonModestoMercedFresnoBakersfield Sponsor Ad Pest Control Tacoma WA Sponsor Ad Hair and Makeup PROS Online Booking Sponsor Ad Jenson General Contracting Sponsor Ad
Upper Left Pest Control Upper Left Pest Control Portland ORUpper Left Pest Control Beaverton ORUpper Left Pest Control Tigard ORUpper Left Pest Control Sherwood ORUpper Left Pest Control Tualatin ORUpper Left Pest Control Lake Oswego ORUpper Left Pest Control West Linn OR Sponsor Ad Youngevity Partners - Youngevity Independent Distrubutor Sponsor Ad
Hemp CBD Oil - CTFO Independent Distrubutor Sponsor Ad
Enagic Independent Distributor Sponsor Ad WE ARE IN LOCAL MARKETING New York City NYLos Angeles CAChicago ILHouston TXPhoenix AZPhiladelphia PASan Antonio TXSan Diego CADallas TXSan Jose CAAustin TXJacksonville FLSan Francisco CAColumbus OHFort Worth TXIndianapolis INCharlotte NCSeattle WADenver COWashington DC Boston MAEl Paso TXDetroit MINashville TNMemphis TNPortland OregonOklahoma City OKLas Vegas NVLouisville KYBaltimore MDMilwaukee WIAlbuquerque NMTucson AZFresno CASacramento CAMesa AZKansas City MOAtlanta GALong Beach CAOmaha NE Raleigh NCColorado Springs COMiami FLVirginia Beach VAOakland CAMinneapolis MNTulsa OKArlington TXNew Orleans LAWichita KSCleveland OHTampa FLBakersfield CAAurora COAnaheim CAHonolulu HawaiiSanta Ana CARiverside CACorpus Christi TXLexington KY Stockton CASt Louis MOSt Paul MNHenderson NVPittsburgh PACincinnati OHAnchorage AKGreensboro NCPlano TXNewark NJLincoln NEOrlando FLIrvine CAToledo OHJersey City NJChula Vista CADurham NCFort Wayne INSt Petersburg FLLaredo TX Sponsor Ad Capital Funding Partners - DAC AgentSponsor Ad TCC Molalla - The Country Church
